Inventory of the Benjamin A. Rogge papers, 1945-2005
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 48-51)
  - Indiana Association of Plumbing Contractors, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 18)
  - Harding College, Searcy, Arkansas, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 19)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 20)
  - First Wisconsin National Bank, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1970 (Folder 50: 21)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 22)
  - Lincoln Club, Los Angeles, California, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 23)
  - Indianapolis Power and Light Company, Edison Science and Youth Day Dinner, 1970 (Folder 50: 24)
  - Business in Society Course, University of Wisconsin, 1970 (Folder 50: 25)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations, undated (Folder 50: 26)
  - Relm Lecture Series, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 27)
  - Clergy Club, Racine, Wisconsin, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 28)
  - Citizens First National Bank, Princeton, Illinois, 1969-1970 (Folder 50: 29)
  - Charles Edison Youth Fund conferences, 1970 (Folder 50: 30)
  - American Economic Association annual meeting, 1969 (Folder 50: 31)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations, Detroit, Michigan, 1969 (Folder 51: 1)
  - Young-Roberts, 1969 (Folder 51: 2)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Wabash Alumni, California, 1969 (Folder 51: 3)
  - Zonta International, Std. Life Insurance Company, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1969, undated (Folder 51: 4)
  - Society for Advancement of Management, Indianapolis Water Company, 1969 (Folder 51: 5)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, West Chester, Pennsylvania, 1969 (Folder 51: 6)
  - Western Ohio Clergy Economic Education Foundation, London, Ohio, 1969 (Folder 51: 7)
  - Frankfort Rotary Club, 1969 (Folder 51: 8)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Pennsylvania, 1969 (Folder 51: 9)
  - South Dakota Bankers Association, economic seminar for young adults, Huron, South Dakota, 1968-1969 (Folder 51: 10)
  - "National Conference of Editorial Writers," Indianapolis, Indiana, 1969 (Folder 51: 11)
  - Master Chemical Corporation, Perrysburg, Ohio, 1969-1972 (Folder 51: 12)
  - Business 100, "Business in Society," University of Wisconsin, Madison, 1969 (Folder 51: 13)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1969 (Folder 51: 14)
- Correspondence on Emerson Schmidt book, 1972 (Folder 51: 15)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 51-54)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminars, 1969 (Folder 51: 16-18)
  - Public Utility Executive Program and Relm Foundation, 1969 (Folder 51: 19)
  - Clergy Economic Education Foundation, Stevens Point, Wisconsin, 1968-1969 (Folder 51: 20)
  - Correspondent banks forum, Citizens Bank, Sheboygan, Michigan, 1969 (Folder 51: 21)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1957-1969 (Folder 51: 22)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1969 (Folder 51: 23)
  - Bank of Lansing, Michigan, 1969 (Folder 51: 24)
  - Purdue Conservative Club, 1969 (Folder 51: 25)
  - Wisconsin Installment Bankers Association, 1969 (Folder 51: 26)
  - Adam Smith and the Wealth of Nations film launch, 1975-1976 (Folder 52: 1)
  - Public Service Indiana marketing conference, 1975 (Folder 52: 2)
  - The Faultless Rubber Company, Ashland, Ohio, 1975-1976 (Folder 52: 3)
  - Central Indiana Women Bank Officers, Crawfordsville, Indiana, 1975-1976 (Folder 52: 4)
  - Bank Administration Institute, Chicago, Illinois, 1975 (Folder 52: 5)
  - St. Joseph Valley Bank Economic seminar, 1975 (Folder 52: 6)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1975 (Folder 52: 7)
  - Cincinnati Rotary Club, 1975 (Folder 52: 8)
  - South Dakota Bankers Association, annual economic seminar for young adults, 1974-1975 (Folder 52: 9)
  - Erik v. Kuehnelt-Leddihn Lecture, 1954, 1975-1976 (Folder 52: 10)
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations, 1975 (Folder 52: 11)
  - Philadelphia Society, Chicago, Illinois, 1974-1975 (Folder 52: 12)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, 1975 (Folder 52: 13)
  - Michigan Bankers Association, MBA Operations/BAI conference, 1970-1975 (Folder 52: 14)
  - Alumni meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1975 (Folder 52: 15)
  - Foundation for Economic Education undergraduate seminar, 1975 (Folder 52: 16)
  - Luncheon meeting with Alan Stanford, 1975 (Folder 52: 17)
  - New England Gas Association conference, 1974-1975 (Folder 52: 18)
  - Colorado, 1974-1975 (Folder 52: 19)
  - Southern California Edison Company executive conference, 1973-1975 (Folder 52: 20)
  - American Institute of Banking (AIB), Lafayette, California, 1975 (Folder 52: 21)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1975 (Folder 52: 22)
  - Ohio Bankers Association Convention, Columbus, Ohio, 1974-1975 (Folder 52: 23)
  - Young Presidents' Organization construction seminar, 1975 (Folder 52: 24)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1974-1975 (Folder 52: 25)
  - Sales and Marketing Executives-International, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1974 (Folder 52: 26)
  - Michigan National Bank, Detroit, 1974-1975 (Folder 52: 27)
  - Pulliam Fellows, 1975 (Folder 52: 28)
  - Rubber Manufacturers Association, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 1975 (Folder 52: 29)
  - Mercantile Bank, 1975 (Folder 52: 30)
  - Indiana Mortgage Bankers, Notre Dame, Indiana, 1975 (Folder 52: 31)
  - Dallas Power and Light Management Development seminar, 1975 (Folder 52: 32)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Bertel Sparks Lecture, 1975 (Folder 52: 33)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, 1975 (Folder 52: 34)
  - Wabash College Alumni Weekend, 1975 (Folder 52: 35)
  - Indiana Bankers Association, Terre Haute, Indiana, 1975 (Folder 52: 36)
  - Concrete Reinforcement Institute, 1970, 1975 (Folder 52: 37)
  - Carolina Power and Light Company, Boca Raton, Louisiana, 1975 (Folder 52: 38)
  - F. A. Hayek Testimonial Dinner, Hillsdale College, Michigan, 1975 (Folder 52: 39)
  - Dana Corporation management meeting, 1975 (Folder 52: 40)
  - Indiana National Corporation, Officer's Association, 1975 (Folder 53: 1)
  - Vistron Corporation, Lima, Ohio, 1975 (Folder 53: 2)
  - Central Indiana Bankers Association, 1975 (Folder 53: 3)
  - Sugar Creek Kiwanis, 1975 (Folder 53: 4)
  - "Faculty Challenges,", undated (Folder 53: 5)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, J. I. Case Company, 1975 (Folder 53: 6)
  - Free Enterprise Committee of the Indianapolis Rotary, 1965, 1975 (Folder 53: 7)
  - Michigan Bankers Association, consumer credit conference, 1975 (Folder 53: 8)
  - London, circa 1975-1976 (Folder 53: 9)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Bethany College, 1975 (Folder 53: 10)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1975 (Folder 53: 11)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society, Hillsdale College, Michigan, 1975 (Folder 53: 12)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1975 (Folder 53: 13)
  - Florists, Richmond, Indiana, 1975 (Folder 53: 14)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1974-1975 (Folder 53: 15)
  - First National Bank and Trust Annual Industrial Dinner, Alton, Illinois, 1974-1975 (Folder 53: 16)
  - Robert Morris Associates, Warsaw, Indiana, 1974 (Folder 53: 17)
  - Free Enterprise Resource Center public forum, Phoenix, Arizona, 1974 (Folder 53: 18)
  - Young Presidents' Organization, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1974 (Folder 53: 19)
  - Indianapolis Bond Club, 1974 (Folder 53: 20)
  - South Dakota Bankers Association, Pierre, South Dakota, 1973-1974 (Folder 53: 21)
  - ASPA seminar, 1974 (Folder 53: 22)
  - Ohio Edison Company Electric Energy Association, 1974 (Folder 53: 23)
  - Milk Industry Foundation, 1974 (Folder 53: 24)
  - Interstate Natural Gas Association of America annual meeting, Palm Beach, Florida, 1974-1975 (Folder 53: 25)
  - Roger Imeson, C. P. A., circa 1974 (Folder 53: 26)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Hillsdale College, Michigan, 1974 (Folder 53: 27)
  - Committee for Futures Studies meeting, Indiana University, Bloomington, 1974 (Folder 53: 28)
  - Adam Smith and the Wealth of Nations film, trip to London, England, 1975 (Folder 53: 29)
    Includes script
  - Southern Economic Association annual conference, 1974 (Folder 53: 30)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Northern California Economic seminars, San Francisco, California, 1974 (Folder 54: 1)
  - Tampa Electric Company, 1973-1974 (Folder 54: 2)
  - Edison Electric Institute conference, Chicago, Illinois, 1973-1974 (Folder 54: 3)
  - Caterpillar Dealer seminar, 1974 (Folder 54: 4)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society, Brussels, Belgium, 1974 (Folder 54: 5)
  - Illinois-Eastern Iowa District Convention, Decatur, Illinois, 1973-1974 (Folder 54: 6)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1974-1975 (Folder 54: 7)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, 1974 (Folder 54: 8)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1974 (Folder 54: 9)
  - Wolf and Company Partners conference, 1974-1976 (Folder 54: 10)
  - Public Finance Institute, University of Michigan, 1974 (Folder 54: 11)
  - Wisconsin Banking Association, 1974 (Folder 54: 12)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Idaho, 1974 (Folder 54: 13)
  - Peter Voss Lecture, 1973-1974 (Folder 54: 14)
  - Foundation for Economic Education annual meeting, 1974 (Folder 54: 15)
  - Indiana Mortgage Bankers, Clarksville, Indiana, 1973-1974 (Folder 54: 16)
  - Employers Association, Inc., 1973-1974 (Folder 54: 17)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Illinois, 1974 (Folder 54: 18)
  - Philadelphia Society, Chicago, Illinois, 1966-1974 (Folder 54: 19)
    Meeting held in 1974
  - Relm and Earhart Foundations meeting, 1974 (Folder 54: 20)
  - Hoover Presidential Library Association, Inc., 1973 (Folder 54: 21)
  - Lux et Veritas, Inc., 1974 (Folder 54: 22)
  - Foundation for Economic Education undergraduate seminar, 1974 (Folder 54: 23)
  - Indiana Central College, 1974 (Folder 54: 24)
  - Pacific Coast Electrical Association executive seminar, Monterey, California, 1974 (Folder 54: 25)
  - Muncie Bar Association, 1974 (Folder 54: 26)
  - Hoover Presidential Library Association, Inc., 1973-1974 (Folder 54: 27)
  - Service Club Group, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1973-1974 (Folder 54: 28)
  - New York City, 1974 (Folder 54: 29)
  - Liberty Fund, "Basic Principles of a Monetary System" seminar, 1974 (Folder 54: 30)
- McKinley Visiting Scholar (cancelled), Mount Union College, Alliance, Ohio, 1972-1973 (Folder 55: 1)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 55)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1973-1974 (Folder 55: 2)
  - American Economic Association, 1973 (Folder 55: 3)
  - United Telephone of Ohio, 1973-1974 (Folder 55: 4)
  - Lilly Endowment, 1973 (Folder 55: 5)
  - Michigan Bankers Association bank management conference, 1973 (Folder 55: 6)
  - Nevada Taxpayers Association, Reno, 1973-1974 (Folder 55: 7)
  - Ludwig von Mises Distinguished Visiting Lectures in Political Economy, Hillsdale College, Michigan, 1973 (Folder 55: 8)
  - Illinois Bankers Association, 1973 (Folder 55: 9)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1973 (Folder 55: 10)
  - South Dakota Bankers Association and Foundation for Economic Education, 1973-1974 (Folder 55: 11)
  - Milton Friedman visit to Wabash College, 1972-1973 (Folder 55: 12)
  - Erik Ritter von Kuehnelt-Liddihn visit, 1973 (Folder 55: 13)
- Biographical file (Folder 55)
  - Rogge bibliography and description of speeches, 2005 (Folder 55: 14)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 55-56)
  - West Central Ohio Clergy economic education conference, 1972-1973 (Folder 55: 15)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, 1973 (Folder 55: 16)
  - Estate Planning Council of Indianapolis, 1973 (Folder 55: 17)
  - Meeting of officers and directors of bank and loan companies and city/county officials, Peru, Indiana, 1973 (Folder 55: 18)
  - Indianapolis Rotary Club, 1973 (Folder 55: 19)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Utah, 1973 (Folder 55: 20)
  - Indiana Council for Economic Education, Purdue University, 1973 (Folder 55: 21)
  - Mont Pèlerin Society regional meetings, Guatemala, Central America, 1973 (Folder 55: 22)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1973 (Folder 55: 23)
  - National Association of Plastics Distributors Annual Convention, 1973 (Folder 55: 24)
  - Indianapolis Chamber of Commerce, 1973 (Folder 55: 25)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, board meeting, 1973 (Folder 55: 26)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1972-1973 (Folder 55: 27)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1973 (Folder 55: 28)
  - Amalgamated Bank economic seminar, 1973 (Folder 55: 29)
  - American Cutlery Manufacturers Association, Washington, D. C., 1973 (Folder 55: 30)
  - Philadelphia Society meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1973 (Folder 55: 31)
  - Kansas Bankers Association, Wichita, Kansas, 1973 (Folder 55: 32)
  - Plumbing, Heating, Cooling Contractors Association of Greater Indianapolis, 1973 (Folder 55: 33)
  - Franklin Company, Foundation for Freedom, Chicago, Illinois, 1972-1973 (Folder 55: 34)
  - Foundation for Economic Education undergraduate seminar, 1973 (Folder 56: 1)
  - Nebraska Bankers Association, Omaha, 1972-1973 (Folder 56: 2)
  - Wabash College Chicago Area Alumni Association luncheon meeting, 1972 (Folder 56: 3)
  - State University College, Geneseo, New York, 1972-1973 (Folder 56: 4)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1973 (Folder 56: 5)
  - Sioux City Bankers Association, Iowa Bankers Association annual meeting, Sioux City, Iowa, 1973 (Folder 56: 6)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Society of Peoria, 1972-1973 (Folder 56: 7)
  - Ohio Young Americans for Freedom, Columbus, Ohio, 1973 (Folder 56: 8)
  - University of San Francisco, "Symposium on the Origin and Development of Property Rights,", 1972-1973 (Folder 56: 9)
  - Bank Administration Institute, 1972-1973 (Folder 56: 10)
  - Liberty Fund Socratic seminar, 1975-1978 (Folder 56: 11)
- Subject file (Folder 56)
  - Industry Studies, 1946-1950 (Folder 56: 12)
  - Cartels, 1953 (Folder 56: 13)
  - The Human Life Review and clippings, 1973, 1977 (Folder 56: 14)
- Writings by others (Folder 56-58)
  - Milton Friedman, 1973-1979 (Folder 56: 15)
  - Harold Demsetz, 1969-1973, undated (Folder 56: 16)
  - R. H. Coase, 1959 (Folder 56: 17)
  - Gottfried Haberler, 1956 (Folder 56: 18)
  - W. Allen Wallis, 1966-1975 (Folder 56: 19)
  - Arthur Shenfield, 1970-1972 (Folder 57: 1)
  - Murray L. Weidenbaum, 1975 (Folder 57: 2)
  - Henry G. Manne, 1969-1971 (Folder 57: 3)
  - Wilhelm Röpke, 1958-1965 (Folder 57: 4)
  - Murray Rothbard, 1965-1974 (Folder 57: 5)
  - Yale Brozen, 1955-1978 (Folder 57: 6)
  - George J. Stigler, 1964-1969, undated (Folder 57: 7)
    Includes Mont Pèlerin Society speech
  - Stephen J. Tonsor, 1970-1971, undated (Folder 57: 8)
  - Gustavo R. Velasco, undated (Folder 58: 1)
- Subject file (Folder 58-60)
  - "A Research Guide in Public Policy" by Robert Schuettinger, 1975 (Folder 58: 2)
  - Big business regulation, 1980 (Folder 58: 3)
  - Equality, 1972-1973 (Folder 58: 4)
  - Conservation, pollution, etc., 1966-1976 (Folder 58: 5)
  - Health and medicine, 1965-1975 (Folder 58: 6)
  - Conservatives and libertarians, writings, 1953-1975 (Folder 58: 7)
  - Monetary and fiscal, price controls, 1960-1975 (Folder 59: 1)
    Includes letter from Gurrie Rhoads to Milton Friedman
  - Profits, 1973 (Folder 59: 2)
  - Multi-national corporations, 1973, undated (Folder 59: 3)
  - Anti-trust, patents, 1959-1962 (Folder 59: 4)
  - Economic development, 1949-1969 (Folder 59: 5)
  - Technological change, 1952-1953, 1971 (Folder 59: 6)
  - Education, 1961-1979 (Folder 60: 1)
  - Trade union material, 1946-1949 (Folder 60: 2)
    Includes student work
  - Building codes, unions, 1970-1972 (Folder 60: 3)
- Biographical file (Folder 60-61)
  - Rogge appointment books, 1957, 1961 (Folder 60: 4)
  - Rogge appointment books and calendars, 1956-1978 (Folder 61)
- Printed matter, 1976 (Folder 61)
- Subject file (Folder 62)
  - Economic outlook, second level, 1968-1969 (Folder 62: 1)
  - Agriculture, 1945-1947 (Folder 62: 2)
  - College administration, campus unrest, etc., 1969-1972 (Folder 62: 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966-1980 (Folder 62: 4-5)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 62)
  - National Hardwood Lumber Association, 1976 (Folder 62: 6)
  - Liberty Fund, board meeting, 1980 (Folder 62: 7)
  - Conferences on free enterprise, Centenary College of Louisiana, 1976-1977 (Folder 62: 8)
- Subject file (Folder 63-64)
  - Economic education programs, 1974-1977 (Folder 63: 1)
  - Anti-trust, 1967-1978 (Folder 63: 2)
    Includes agenda for Liberty Fund seminar
  - Anti-trust and miscellaneous, 1971-1980 (Folder 63: 3)
  - Compensation systems, 1952-1974 (Folder 63: 4)
  - Credit allocation, 1972-1977, undated (Folder 63: 5)
  - Competition, basic, 1951-1976 (Folder 64: 1)
  - Energy crisis, 1973-1975 (Folder 64: 2)
- Speaking engagements, conferences, and meetings file (Folder 64-67)
  - American Management Association, 1963 (Folder 64: 3)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1963-1964 (Folder 64: 4)
  - Mt. Ranier seminar, Seattle, Washington, 1963 (Folder 64: 5)
  - Walker Manufacturing Company of Racine, Wisconsin, Purdue, 1963 (Folder 64: 6)
  - AMA conference, 1963 (Folder 64: 7)
    Possibly American Management Association
  - Indianapolis Chamber of Commerce, 1963 (Folder 64: 7)
  - Indianapolis Chamber of Commerce, 1963 (Folder 64: 8)
  - Midwest Economics Association annual meeting, St. Louis, Missouri, 1963 (Folder 64: 9)
  - Dow Chemical Company, Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Midland, Michigan, 1963 (Folder 64: 10)
  - North Side Dental Society of Indianapolis, 1963 (Folder 64: 11)
  - DePauw University, 1963 (Folder 64: 12)
  - Indiana Conservative Club, Indianapolis, 1962-1963 (Folder 64: 13)
  - Indianapolis Economic Education Advisory Committee, Television College of Air, "The American Economy,", 1962-1963 (Folder 64: 14)
  - Indiana University, graduate study conference, 1962-1963 (Folder 64: 15)
  - ISI, Beloit, Wisconsin, 1963 (Folder 64: 16)
    Possibly Intercollegiate Society of Individualists
  - Teachers' Institute, Decatur, Illinois, 1963 (Folder 65: 1)
  - American Management Association (AMA), New York, 1960-1963 (Folder 65: 2)
  - Kiwanis Club of Marion, Indiana, 1963 (Folder 65: 3)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, Clergy-Industry Relations Committee, Bermuda, 1962-1963 (Folder 65: 4)
  - "American Conference of Academic Deans," Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1962-1963 (Folder 65: 5)
  - Sales and Marketing Executives of Indianapolis, Industry-Education Night, 1962-1963 (Folder 65: 6)
  - Anti Communist Study Program, Lebanon, Indiana, 1962 (Folder 65: 7)
  - American Management Association (AMA), Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1961-1962 (Folder 65: 8)
  - League of Women Voters, 1962 (Folder 65: 9)
  - ISI, Purdue University, 1962 (Folder 65: 10)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists (ISI), Earlham College, Richmond, Indiana, 1962 (Folder 65: 11)
  - Anderson Rotary Club, Indiana, 1962 (Folder 65: 12)
  - Governor's conference on Indiana's economic future, 1962 (Folder 65: 13)
  - Junior League of Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1962-1963 (Folder 65: 14)
  - Associated Industries of Massachusetts annual meeting, Boston, 1962 (Folder 65: 15)
  - American conference on education, Chicago, Illinois, 1962 (Folder 65: 16)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists Summer School, Lake Forest, Illinois, 1962 (Folder 65: 17)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1961-1962 (Folder 65: 18)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1959-1963 (Folder 65: 19-20)
  - American Management Association (AMA), Foundation for Economic Education, New York City, 1962 (Folder 65: 21)
  - R. K. Burns, University of Chicago, 1962 (Folder 65: 22)
  - Wabash Alumni Association Dinner, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1961-1962 (Folder 65: 23)
  - American Management Association (AMA) Economic Trend Clinic, Foundation for Economic Education, 1962 (Folder 65: 24)
  - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) of the University of Illinois, 1961-1962 (Folder 65: 25)
  - American Management Association (AMA), Foundation for Economic Education seminar, 1962 (Folder 65: 26)
  - Kingman High School commencement, 1962 (Folder 65: 27)
  - Barber-Colman Company seminar, Rockford, Illinois, 1961-1962 (Folder 65: 28)
  - Irwin Union Bank, Columbus, Indiana, 1962 (Folder 65: 29)
  - Muncie Recruiting Session, A. E. Boyce Company, 1962 (Folder 65: 30)
  - Ohio State University Young Republican Club, 1961-1962 (Folder 65: 31)
  - Indiana University Conservative League, 1962 (Folder 65: 32)
  - University of Minnesota Management Development Program, 1961-1962 (Folder 65: 33)
  - Indiana Real Estate Board, 1962 (Folder 66: 1)
  - Foundation for Economic Education seminar, Lima, Ohio, 1962 (Folder 66: 2)
  - Foundation for Economic Education and Colgate, New York City, 1962 (Folder 66: 3)
  - Junior League of Indianapolis seminar, 1961-1962 (Folder 66: 4)
  - American Conference of Academic Deans (1962), Cleveland, Ohio, 1961 (Folder 66: 5)
  - Wichita seminar, 1961 (Folder 66: 6)
  - Houston seminar and Wichita seminar, Foundation for Economic Education, 1961 (Folder 66: 7)
  - Wabash College alumni meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1961 (Folder 66: 8)
  - Indianapolis Control, Controllers Institute of America, 1961 (Folder 66: 9)
  - Muncie Hazelwood Christian Church, 1961-1962 (Folder 66: 10)
  - William Volker Fund, 1961 (Folder 66: 11)
    Includes Wabash Alumni Association materials
  - Nassau Club, Princeton, New Jersey, 1961-1962 (Folder 66: 12)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Crawfordsville, Indiana, 1961 (Folder 66: 13)
  - Rotary Club, Tipton, Indiana, 1961 (Folder 66: 14)
  - Indiana Academy of Social Sciences, Indiana University, 1961 (Folder 66: 15)
  - Graduate School of Banking, University of Wisconsin-Madison, sponsored by Central States Conference of Bankers Associations, 1961 -1962 (Folder 66: 16)
  - Public Utility Executive Program, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1961-1962 (Folder 66: 17)
  - Oscar C. Schmidt Memorial Lectures, Rose Polytechnic Institute, Terre Haute, Indiana, 1960-1961 (Folder 66: 18)
  - Indiana Bell Telephone Company, 1961 (Folder 66: 19)
  - Foundation for Economic Education remnant seminar, 1961 (Folder 66: 20)
  - North Central Association of Academic Deans annual meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1961 (Folder 66: 21)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists conference, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1960-1961 (Folder 66: 22)
  - Institute for American Strategy, National Military, industrial and educational conference, Chicago, 1961 (Folder 66: 23)
  - College Committee on Outstanding Students, conference on the superior student, Buck Hill Falls, Pennsylvania, 1960-1961 (Folder 66: 24)
  - Indiana University, graduate study conference, Bloomington, 1961 (Folder 66: 25)
  - Indianapolis Star American Essay Contest, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1960-1961 (Folder 66: 26)
    Rogge was a judge for this contest
  - "Road to Prosperity" TV program, National Association of Manufacturers, Columbus, Ohio, 1961 (Folder 66: 27)
  - "Road to Prosperity" TV program, National Association of Manufacturers, Columbus, Ohio, 1961 (Folder 66: 28)
  - American Conference of Academic Deans, 1960-1961 (Folder 66: 29)
  - PTO, Union City, Indiana, 1960 (Folder 66: 30)
  - Discussion Club, St. Louis, Missouri, 1960 (Folder 66: 31)
  - Edison Electrical Institute Area Development Workshop, St. Louis, Missouri, 1960 (Folder 66: 32)
  - Exchange Clubs, Edinburg, Indiana, 1960 (Folder 66: 33)
  - General Motors conference for educators in the liberal arts, 1960 (Folder 66: 34)